UNITE Publications 6000 PUBS
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Box: 2, Folder: 72, Publication (Box 2, Folder 72)
  - Item 1: Worker Education Program., 1996; Publication (Box 2, Folder 72)
    Notes: December 1996.
  - Item 2: Worker Education Program., 1996; Publication (Box 2, Folder 72)
    Notes: December 1996. Copy 2.
  - Item 3: Worker Education Program., 1996; Publication (Box 2, Folder 72)
    Notes: December 1996. Copy 3.
- Box: 2, Folder: 73, Publication (Box 2, Folder 73)
  - Item 1: Worker Education Program: New Steps of the Union, UNITE., 1997; Publication (Box 2, Folder 73)
    Notes: February 1997.
- Box: 2, Folder: 74, Publication (Box 2, Folder 74)
  - Item 1: Worker Education Program: New Steps of the Union, UNITE., 1997; Publication (Box 2, Folder 74)
    Notes: April 1997.
- Box: 2, Folder: 75, Publication (Box 2, Folder 75)
  - Item 1: Worker Education Program: New Steps of the Union, UNITE., 1997; Publication (Box 2, Folder 75)
    Notes: Summer 1997.
- Box: 2, Folder: 76, Publication (Box 2, Folder 76)
  - Item 1: Worker Education Program: New Steps of the Union, UNITE., 1998; Publication (Box 2, Folder 76)
    Notes: Spring 1998.
- Box: 2, Folder: 77, Publication (Box 2, Folder 77)
  - Item 1: Workers' Rights Handbook, Publication (Box 2, Folder 77)
    Author: UNITE (Union of Needletrades, Industrial and Textile Employees); Garment Workers' Center
    Notes: Chinese-language version on opposing pages
    Language: English; Chinese.
- Box: 2, Folder: 78, Publication (Box 2, Folder 78)
  - Item 1: Working Families Agenda., Publication (Box 2, Folder 78)
- Box: 2, Folder: 79, Publication (Box 2, Folder 79)
  - Item 1: Convention Reporter, 1999; Publication (Box 2, Folder 79)
    Notes: First UNITE Constitutional Convention, Miami Beach, FL, June 28, 1999
  - Item 2: Convention Reporter, 1999; Publication (Box 2, Folder 79)
    Notes: First UNITE Constitutional Convention, Miami Beach, FL, June 29, 1999
  - Item 3: Convention Reporter, 1999; Publication (Box 2, Folder 79)
    Notes: First UNITE Constitutional Convention, Miami Beach, FL, June 30, 1999
  - Item 4: Convention Reporter, 1999; Publication (Box 2, Folder 79)
    Notes: First UNITE Constitutional Convention, Miami Beach, FL, July 1, 1999
- Box: 3, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Benefits Conference, 2002; Publication (Box 3, Folder 1)
    Author: Amalgamated Life Insurance Company; Textile Workers Pension Fund
    Notes: Conference notebook and handouts
- Box: 3, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Benefits Conference, 2002; Publication (Box 3, Folder 2)
    Author: UNITE Legal Department
- Box: 3, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Collective Bargaining Conference, 2001; Publication (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Box: 3, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Employee Benefit Trustee Conference, 2002; Publication (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Box: 3, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Employee Handbook, 2000; Publication (Box 3, Folder 5)
    Author: UNITE
- Box: 3, Folder: 6, Publication (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Bargaining Conference, 2001; Publication (Box 3, Folder 6)
    Author: Textile Workers Pension Fund
- Box: 3, Folder: 7, Publication (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Building the Local Union, Publication (Box 3, Folder 7)
    Author: Department of Education
  - Item 2: A Participant's Handbook for a Train-the-Trainer Program, Publication (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Box: 3, Folder: 8, Publication (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Ergonomic Handbook for the Clothing Industry, 2001; Publication (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Item 2: Dealing with Work-Related Musculoskeletal Disorders in the Ontario Clothing Industry, 2000; Publication (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Item 3: Stop the Pain! A Workers' Guide to Job Design., 1995; Publication (Box 3, Folder 8)
    Author: Department of Occupational Health and Safety
  - Item 4: Ergonomic Facts and Action Manual., 2001; Publication (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Box: 3, Folder: 9, Publication (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: How to Defend a Civil Rights Case When You Don't Have a Lawyer, 1999; Publication (Box 3, Folder 9)
    Author: Margaret Cammer; Carl Cresci; Judith Gische; Doris Ling-Cohan; David Tecklin
- Box: 3, Folder: 10, Publication (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Uneasy Terrain: The Impact of Capital Mobility on Workers, Wages, and Union Organizing, 2000; Publication (Box 3, Folder 10)
    Author: Kate Bronfenbrenner
    Notes: Submitted to the U.S. Trade Deficit Review Commission, September 6, 2000.
- Box: 3, Folder: 11, Publication (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Weaving a Stronger Fabric: The Creation of a Global Apparel Production Agreement, Publication (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Box: 3, Folder: 12, Publication (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Basic Steward Training Manual, Publication (Box 3, Folder 12)
    Notes: Workshop notebook. Includes 3.5" floppy disk
- Box: 3, Folder: 13, Publication (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Basic Steward Training Manual. Workshop Materials., Publication (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Item 2: Basic Steward Training Manual. Workshop Materials., Publication (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Item 3: Basic Steward Training Manual. Workshop Materials., Publication (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Box: 3, Folder: 14, Publication (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Making It Right: Lessons and Solutions in Global Sourcing and Labor Issues Conference, 2002; Publication (Box 3, Folder 14)
    Author: Chain Store Age; DSN Retailing Today; World Monitors
- Box: 3, Folder: 15, Publication (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: Cross Boarder Blues: A Call for Justice for Maquiladora Workers in Tehuacan, 1998; Publication (Box 3, Folder 15)
    Author: National Interfaith Committee for Worker Justice
- Box: 3, Folder: 16, Publication (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: Women Fighting Poverty Conference 9: Women in Action, Now More Than Ever, 2002; Publication (Box 3, Folder 16)
    Author: Women Fighting Poverty Conference
    Notes: Report.
- Box: 3, Folder: 17, Publication (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: Making It Right: The Kellwood Way, 2002; Publication (Box 3, Folder 17)
    Author: Hal J. Upbin
- Box: 3, Folder: 18, Publication (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: Sewing It Together: A Practical Guide to Globalization in the Garment Sector, 2001; Publication (Box 3, Folder 18)
    Author: Catherine Matheson
- Box: 3, Folder: 19, Publication (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: Setting Standards for a Just World, Publication (Box 3, Folder 19)
    Author: Social Accountability International
    Notes: SA8000
- Box: 3, Folder: 20, Publication (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: New York State Senate Certificate of Achievement, 2003; Publication (Box 3, Folder 20)
    Author: Martin J. Golden
- Box: 3, Folder: 21, Publication (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: Jack Sheinkman, 1927-2004, Publication (Box 3, Folder 21)
    Notes: Collected news clippings. Copy 2.
- Box: 3, Folder: 22, Publication (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: Guide to Union Establishments in the Los Angeles and Anaheim Areas, 1998; Publication (Box 3, Folder 22)
    Author: HERE
  - Item 2: Guide to Union Establishments in the Los Angeles and Anaheim Areas, 1998; Publication (Box 3, Folder 22)
- Box: 3, Folder: 23, Publication (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Item 1: Report of the First Constitutional Convention, 1999; Publication (Box 3, Folder 23)
- Box: 3, Folder: 24, Publication (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Item 1: 20th Anniversary Cocktail Gala, 2005; Publication (Box 3, Folder 24)
    Author: Garment Industry Development Corporation
    Notes: March 24, 2005.
- Box: 3, Folder: 25, Publication (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Item 1: UNITE in the New Millenium: Celebrating Our Lives in Canada., 2000; Publication (Box 3, Folder 25)
    Language: English; French.
- Box: 3, Folder: 26, Publication (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Item 1: Absent From the Agenda: A Report on the Role of Women in American Unions, 1980; Publication (Box 3, Folder 26)
    Author: Elyse Glassberg; Naomi Baden; Karin Gerstel
    Notes: September, 1980.
  - Item 2: What Do Unions Do For Women?, 1995; Publication (Box 3, Folder 26)
    Author: Roberta Spalter- Roth; Heidi Hartmann; Nancy Collins
    Notes: January 21, 1994.
  - Item 3: Women and Labor-Management Relations: Lessons from Canada, 1993; Publication (Box 3, Folder 26)
    Author: Susan C. Eaton
    Notes: 31-Dec-93
  - Item 4: Celebrating Labor Union Women's History, Publication (Box 3, Folder 26)
    Author: Marjorie H. Stern
- Box: 3, Folder: 27, Publication (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Item 1: La Union Predice Los Trucos de la Compania, Publication (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Item 2: How to Run a Union Meeting, 1980; Publication (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Item 3: Workers' Rights Handbook, Publication (Box 3, Folder 27)
    Language: English;Chinese.
  - Item 4: Bienvenidos a UNITE. Trabajando por Nuestro Futuro, Publication (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Item 5: Campaign for the Future, Publication (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Item 6: Campaign for the Future, Publication (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Item 7: Campaign for the Future, Publication (Box 3, Folder 27)
- Box: 3, Folder: 28, Publication (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Item 1: Keeping Jobs in Fashion. Annual Report 1999-2000, Publication (Box 3, Folder 28)
- Box: 3, Folder: 29, Publication (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Item 1: Global Justice for Garment Workers, 2001; Publication (Box 3, Folder 29)
    Notes: Information packet
- Box: 3, Folder: 30, Publication (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Item 1: New York State AFL-CIO Information Packet, 1998; Publication (Box 3, Folder 30)
    Author: AFL- CIO
- Box: 3, Folder: 31, Publication (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Item 1: New York Times. Nike Shoe Plant in Vietnam is Called Unsafe For Workers., 1997; Publication (Box 3, Folder 31)
    Author: New York Times
    Notes: November 8, 1997. Reprinted article.
- Box: 4, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Misery by Design, 1996; Publication (Box 4, Folder 1)
    Author: Union of Needletrades, Industrial and Textile Employees
- Box: 4, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Bargaining Unit Directory, 1996; Publication (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Box: 4, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: UNITE!, 1999-2002 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Box: 4, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: UNITE!, 1995-1998 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Box: 4, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: A Handbook for Members, 1995; Publication (Box 4, Folder 5)
    Author: Rochester Regional Joint Board
    Notes: November 1995.
  - Item 2: The Daily Dozen, 1996; Publication (Box 4, Folder 5)
    Author: UNITE Local 496
    Notes: Winter 1996
  - Item 3: Clothes Line Grape Vine, 1996; Publication (Box 4, Folder 5)
    Author: UNITE Local 1018
    Notes: January/March 1996
  - Item 4: UNITE, 1996; Publication (Box 4, Folder 5)
    Notes: Issue no.2 (1996:Feb.)
  - Item 5: The Spirit of 89 - 22 - 1, 1995; Publication (Box 4, Folder 5)
    Author: New York Coat, Suit, Dress, Rainwear and Allied Workers Union
    Notes: v.10:no.2 (1995:Fall)